modiphius.net 2019-07-05

# Privacy policy - Modiphius Entertainment

Modiphius Entertainment stores relevant information supplied by you in order to fulfil your retail orders or facilitate your secure login to Modiphius Entertainment website services and features.

**Modiphius Entertainment Ltd. Full Privacy policy**

At Modiphius Entertainment we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to provide a more personalised experience. Any personal information provided to or gathered by Modiphius Entertainment through this website or otherwise is processed by Modiphius Entertainment Ltd, 39 Harwood Road, London, SW6 4QP, United Kingdom. Modiphius Entertainment Ltd is also the data controller.

**Our Policies**

We aim to process your personal data fairly and lawfully and in line with codes of industry best practice.

We undertake to be transparent about how we collect your personal data and use it in a way that you would reasonably expect and we provide a public privacy policy for all our digital platforms to explain this. 

We undertake to only contact you with relevant information about products you have expressed an interest in including our newsletter.

You may at any time, change your email preferences with us and we positively encourage you to do so, so that you only receive information about games and genres you like.  To do this open any newsletter we have sent you and choose the Update Profile option at the bottom to manage your contact preferences or unsubscribe.

**Your Privacy Choices**

You may  **[contact us ](http://www.modiphius.com/contact)**to have your personal information removed from our services.

You may at any time request to see the information we hold about you and we undertake to provide this information within 30 days.

We undertake to store your digital data in secure locations, and to only allow appropriate members of staff to access it.

Your data is stored as follows:

Modiphius.net Webstore Customers: Your account information is stored in the Shopify.com store platform. Shopify does not store payment details. All payment information is securely protected by encrypted transactions with your bank or payment service such as Paypal, Amazon Pay etc.  

Modiphius.com Website: From time to time we run surveys to research new projects and get feedback from the community, or check preferences for Kickstarter Backers. The responses are stored securely within the backend of the Weebly.com software. We use an app to let you get a notification when a product is back in stock which if you use, stores your email address. 

Newsletters: We use ConstantContact.com to securely store your emails for the purposes of sending newsletters. You can update which email list you are on or unsubscribe at any time.

Dropbox: We use a company dropbox to securely store customer data that is being used for analysis, or bulk order fulfilment.

Pledgemanager & Backerkit: To process and handle fulfilment for Kickstarter or other crowdfunding rewards we use various pledge manager cloud services such as Backerkit.com or Pledgemanager.com.

Fulfilment – To process physical orders, we securely transfer your shipping address to our warehouse provider Gamequest.

Forum - To facilitate your participation in the forum you set a login and password or use a social media login. 

The remainder of this privacy policy sets out the way in which we will collect, store and use information about you.

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

When you log in, we need to know your name and e-mail address. This allows us to identify you as the person who used the Modiphius Entertainment website and to include the details in our database for order tracking. All information we hold about you is stored with the e-mail address you used when you registered. As a store customer we may hold your shipping and billing address along with your order history. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, or sign up for a newsletter, we may ask for your name, address and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.  We may ask for other information such as age, location or your preferences in relation to games and other merchandising.  This information is used to personalise our services to you and to create aggregate reports. The reports will not contain any personally identifying information. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us improve the design and layout of the service. We may provide your details to legal bodies such as HMRC on their request to maintain our legal compliance. We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the website, and new services that we may offer. If you would rather not receive this information you may opt out by using the unsubscribe link in the e-mail. 

**How does Modiphius Entertainment protect customer information?**

Whenever you provide your details we use a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us, our cloud services or payment providers. Furthermore, as required by the UK Data Protection Legislation and new EU Data Protection law, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information that you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you. 

**What about "cookies"?**

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies enable us to provide features such as making it easier to recall your profile details from our secure databases. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our service, including amending your Profile.

In particular we use cookies to help us show you the prices of our products in the most relevant currency we can. By using our website, you agree to allow third parties to process your IP address, in order to determine your location for the purpose of the currency conversion. You also agree to have that currency stored in a session cookie in your browser (a temporary cookie which gets automatically removed when you close your browser). We do this in order for the selected currency to remain selected and consistent when browsing our website so that the prices can convert to your (the visitor) local currency.

**Will Modiphius disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**

Modiphius Entertainment may provide aggregate statistics about the users of the Modiphius Entertainment webstore, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mails, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer services. Such companies and individuals will have access only to personal information needed to perform these functions, but may not use it for any other purposes and are required to process the data in accordance with the UK and EU's Data Protection legislation.

**In summary**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make your visit at Modiphius Entertainment as useful as possible and to enhance your overall experience. We will not sell trade or rent your personal information to others, except in the event of a major capital restructuring of Modiphius Entertainment Ltd such as a change of ownership.

**Your consent**

By using our websites, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Modiphius Entertainment Ltd. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Please note that the information you enter may be transferred outside the European Economic Area for the purposes of processing by Modiphius Entertainment and its affiliates and in order to maintain customer accounts for you at other Modiphius Entertainment websites. Any transfer of personal information outside of the European Economic Area is done in circumstances ensuring that the information is processed only in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the UK and EU's Data Protection Act. By submitting your data, you consent to this transfer. Your personal information may also be used by us and our affiliates to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to our website, new Modiphius Entertainment services and special offers we think you’ll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, you may opt out by clicking the unsubscribe link in the e-mail.
